nanowerk.com 2006-06-29

# Nanowerk - Privacy Statement

Nanowerk > Privacy Policy 

Nanowerk Privacy Policy

**I. OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**  
---  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   
**II. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted through the Nanowerk websites, including information you submit when placing an order through our “Buy Now” option, when subscribing to our Nanowerk Spotlight service, or when subscribing to one of our Nanowerk newsletters. The types of personal information we may collect include your name, your organization’s name, address, email address, telephone number and, if you are ordering products through us or subscribing to one of our newsletters, your credit card information.   
**III. THE WAY WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. So, for example, when you place an order with a Nanowerk Affiliate, we will share all the personal information that you submit with your order with that Nanowerk Affiliate, but not with any other outside party.   
We use the information you provide about yourself when subscribing to our Nanowerk Spotlight service, or when subscribing to one of our Nanowerk newsletters, only to provide you with the information or service you have requested. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to transmit to you the requested information or service.   
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.   
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our websites and services that we provide through our websites, and also to promote and better explain our services to our business affiliates. For example, we may tell a business affiliate that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our web site, or that Y number of individuals ordered a certain type of product during a given time period through our web site. However, we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals when sharing aggregated information with our business affiliates.   
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   
**IV. OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
**V. OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.   
**VI. HOW TO CONTACT US**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-942-5414 or send us an e-mail at webmaster@nanowerk.com.   
  
This site allows you to research nanoparticles from our extensive _**Nanomaterial Database™**_ and then link directly to an item's manufacturer(s).
